Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the dean, 1948-1983; Accession 1986-A-026
  - Robert Brustein, 1948-1981
    - Yale Cabaret, 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 477)
    - Yale College
      - 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 478)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 479)
      - Committee Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 480)
    - Yale College Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 481)
    - Yale College Faculty, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 482)
    - Yale Film Council, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 483)
    - YRTAA (Yale Repertory Theatre Associate Artists), 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 484)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre
      - Brochure, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 485)
      - Brochures/Advertising, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 486)
      - Newsletter, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 487)
      - Press Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 488)
      - Program, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 489)
    - Yale: Theater Magazine, 1970-1974 (Box 35, Folder 490)
    - Yale University Memos
      - 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 491)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 492)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 493)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 494)
    - Budget Preparations, 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 495)
    - Campus Police, 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 496)
    - Drama 16
      - 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 497)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 498)
    - Faculty Salaries and Appointments
      - 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 499)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 500)
    - Registrar, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 502)
    - Student Correspondence
      - 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 503)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 504)
    - Warnings, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 505)
  - Howard Stein, Administrative Dean
    - ABC Program, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Acting/Directing Department, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Admissions Correspondence
      - 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Admissions Inquiries, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 5 - 6)
    - AETA flaywriting Conference, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Association, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Appointment to Yale, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - B Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Black and Certificate Student Scholarships, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Black Student Enrollment, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Book on Speech
      - 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Bertolt Brecht Script: "Edward II", 1966 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Robert Brustein Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Catalogue Material, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - CBS Fellowship, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - College Work Study Program, 1967-1967 (Box 40, Folder 22 - 23)
    - College Work Study Projects, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - College Work Study Program, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Comedy Paper (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1960s (Box 40, Folder 27 - 28)
    - Curriculum Memos, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Davenport College
      - 1968 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Possible Seminars (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Departmental Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 33 - 34)
    - Departmental Inquiries, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Design Department, 1968-1969 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Draft Status of Accepted Applicants, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Drama School Bulletin, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Drama 7 Course, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Drama Students Guide (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Employment Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Employment Inquiries
      - 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 42)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Ensemble Training, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Faculty Activities (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Faculty Correspondence
      - 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 47)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 48)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 49)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - Faculty Memos
      - 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 51)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 52)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 53)
    - Faculty /Staff Information Questionnaire, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Jules Feiffer Script: "God Bless" (Box 42, Folder 55)
    - Film Companies, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 56)
    - G Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 57)
    - Grecco, Stephen Manuscript: "The Orientals'' (Box 42, Folder 58)
    - Inquiries about the Drama School, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 59)
    - Invitations
      - 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 60 - 61)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 62)
    - Invitations to the School, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 63)
    - Iowa Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 43, Folder 64)
    - Library
      - 1968 (Box 43, Folder 68)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 69)
    - M Correspondence, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 70)
    - Manuscripts
      - 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 71 - 73)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 74)
    - Memoranda, 1965-1967 (Box 44, Folder 75)
    - N Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 76)
    - New Catalogue, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 77)
    - Off-Broadway Producers, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 78)
    - Office of the Bursar, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 79)
    - Office of the President
      - 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 80)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 81)
    - Office of the Provost
      - 1968 (Box 44, Folder 82)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 83)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 44)
    - Personal, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 84)
    - Personal Correspondence
      - 1960s (Box 44, Folder 85)
      - 1965-1967 (Box 44, Folder 86)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 87 - 88)
      - University of Iowa, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 89)
    - Play Manuscript, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 90)
    - Plays: The Moths, Dead Flowers, 1960s (Box 45, Folder 91)
    - Playwriting Scholarships, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 92)
    - Press and Publicity, 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 93)
    - Production Schedules, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 95)
    - Program Inquiries, 1967-1967 (Box 45, Folder 96)
    - Radio Drama Project (Box 45, Folder 97)
    - RCA Corporation, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 98)
    - Recommendations
      - 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 99)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 100)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 101)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 102)
    - Scholarship Allotments, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 106)
    - Scholarships, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 107)
    - Selective Service Information, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 109 - 110)
    - Speeches, 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 111)
    - Student Correspondence
      - 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 112)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 114)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 115)
    - Student Evaluations, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 116)
    - Summer Newsletter, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 117)
    - Supplement to Drama School Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 118)
    - Teacher Training Program, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 119)
    - Terry, Megan: "Viet Rock" Script, 1960s (Box 47, Folder 120)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 121)
    - University Correspondence, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 124)
    - Unsolicited Manuscripts, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 125 - 127)
    - Visitors, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 128)
    - Visits, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 129)
    - Washington Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 131)
    - Weinstein, Arnold: Scripts (Box 48, Folder 132)
    - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 133)
    - Work Scholarship Applications, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 134)
    - Yale Treasurer's Office, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 135)
    - Yale College Memos, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 136)
    - Yale Financial Aid, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 137)
    - Yale University Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 138)
    - Zibel, Robert and Freeman, David: Scripts, 1960s (Box 49, Folder 139)
  - Lloyd Richards, 1979-1991
    - A
      - 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - A-B, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Aaron Davis Hall: City College Performing Arts Center, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Acting/Directing, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Administration of School, 1967-1969 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - A Lesson from Aloes, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Alumni: Active File, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Day: Class of 1931, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Alumni: Drama School, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Director Ed Cole, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Executive Board: Richard Olson, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Executive Comittee, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Fund Letters Accompanying Donation, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Fund: Status Report, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Fund Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Alumni Fund Thank-You Letters /Donations, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Fund Volunteers/Agents, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Fund: "A Word to the Y's", 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Alumni: Lloyd Richards's Letter, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Alumni Relations Memo, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Alumni: Report on the AYA Alumnae Survey, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - American Arts Alliance, 1979-1981 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - American College Theatre Festival, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - ACA (American Council for the Arts), 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - American Council on Education, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - American Repertory Theatre, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - American Theatre Association, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - An Attempt at Flying, 1979-1981 (Box 52, Folder 34 - 35)
    - Arena Stage, Washington, D.C., 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 38)
      - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Atlantic Theatre Company, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - Auditions, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Audition Tour, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - B Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 52, Folder 43)
    - B
      - 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 44)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Boesman and Lena by Athol Fugard, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Bosoms of Neglect, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - The Brides: Playwrights Project, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Brustein, Robert, 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - Budgets, Approved: School of Drama and Repertory Theatre, 1972-1973 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Budget: Brustein's Notes, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Budget Preparation, 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Budget Worksheets: Footnotes, 1970-1974 (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - C
      - 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 58)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - C Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - C-E, 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - Cabaret, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 62)
    - Cincinnati Playhouse, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 64)
    - Commencement, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 65)
    - Community Relations: "Town and Gown", 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 66)
    - Congratulatory Notes: Lloyd Richards, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 67 - 68)
    - Connecticut Ballet Company, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 69)
    - Contemporary Authors, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 70)
    - Ross Cooper, Memorial Service, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 71)
    - C.P.B. (Corporation for Public Broadcasting): Lloyd Richards Search Committee Meeting, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence with Groups of Students and Miscellaneous Information, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 73)
    - D
      - 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 74)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 75)
    - D Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 76)
    - Danish Playwrights Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 77)
    - Davis Center for the Performing Arts, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 78)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 79)
    - Design, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 80)
    - Desperadoes: Playwrights Project, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 81)
    - Development
      - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 82)
      - Audio-visual Center, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 84)
      - Carol Dye Award, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 85)
      - Friars Club, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 87)
      - League of Professional Theatre Training Programs (Grant), 1980 (Box 55, Folder 89)
      - Lunch at the Century Club, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 90)
    - "Domestic Issues" by Corinne Jacker, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 91)
    - Drama School Development Office, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 92)
    - Drama School Productions, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 93)
    - Drama Students Guide, 1977-1979 (Box 55, Folder 94)
    - Dramaturgy, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 95)
    - Drums in the Night, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 96)
    - E
      - 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 97)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 98)
    - E Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 99)
    - "Edward II", 1980 (Box 55, Folder 100)
    - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 101)
      - Actors' Letters, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 102)
      - Board of Project Directors, 1979-1981 (Box 55, Folder 103)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 105)
      - Directors' Letters, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 106)
      - Executive Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 107)
      - National Playwrights Conference
        - 1979-1982 (Box 56, Folder 108 - 110)
        - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 56, Folder 111)
    - F
      - 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 112)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 113)
    - F Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 114)
    - "Family Rites", 1979 (Box 56, Folder 115)
    - File Information, Miscellaneous, 1969-1978 (Box 56, Folder 116)
    - G
      - 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 118)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 119)
    - G Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 120)
    - "God's Smoke", 1980 (Box 57, Folder 121)
    - H Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 122)
    - H Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 123)
    - H- I, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 124)
    - I Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 125)
    - Invitations/Speaking Engagements, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 126)
    - I-J, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 127)
    - Interviews and Articles: Lloyd Richards, 1978-1980 (Box 57, Folder 128)
    - Invitations, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 129)
    - Invitations, Miscellaneous: Response Sent, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 130)
    - Invitations, Unanswered, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 131)
    - J, 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 132)
    - J Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 133)
    - Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee
      - 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 134 - 136)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 137)
    - "Jungle of Cities", 1980 (Box 58, Folder 138)
    - K, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 139)
    - K-N, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 140)
    - K, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 141)
    - K Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 142)
    - L Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 59, Folder 143)
    - L, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 144)
    - LORT (League of Resident Theatres), 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder 145)
    - Literary Management
      - 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 147)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 148)
    - Literary Manager, Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 149)
    - M Correspondence
      - 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 150)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 151)
    - "Magnificent Cuckold", 1981 (Box 60, Folder 152)
    - "Measure for Measure", 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 153)
    - "Medal of Honor Rag": Reviews, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 154)
    - Memo from Robert Orchard, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 155)
    - N Correspondence
      - 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 156)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 157)
    - National Public Radio, 1980-1982 (Box 60, Folder 158)
    - National Public Television, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 159 - 160)
      - Memos, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 161)
    - Newsletter, Summer, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 162)
    - O Correspondence
      - 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 163)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 164)
    - O-R (Box 60, Folder 165)
    - P Correspondence
      - 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 166)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 167)
    - Paint the Town Bluett: Benefit for Yale Drama School, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 168)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 169)
    - PBS: Board of Directors
      - Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 170)
      - Board and Membership Affairs
        - 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 171)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 172)
    - Phone Messages: Lloyd Richards
      - 1980 (Box 62, Folder 173 - 174)
      - 1981 (Box 62, Folder 175)
    - President, Office of the, 1979-1981 (Box 62, Folder 176 - 178)
    - Provost, Office of the, 1979-1981 (Box 63, Folder 179 - 182)
    - Q Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 183)
    - Q-R Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 184)
    - R Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 185)
    - Reading File, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 186)
      - Lloyd Richards
        - 1979 (Box 63, Folder 187)
        - 1980 Jan - Feb (Box 63, Folder 188)
        - 1980 Mar - Apr (Box 63, Folder 189)
        - 1980 May - Jun (Box 63, Folder 190)
        - 1980 Jul - Aug (Box 64, Folder 191)
        - 1980 Sep - Oct (Box 64, Folder 192)
        - 1980 Nov - Dec (Box 64, Folder 193)
        - 1981 Jan - Feb (Box 64, Folder 194)
        - 1981 Mar - Jun (Box 64, Folder 195)
    - Recommendations, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 196)
    - "The Resurrections of Lady Lester" by Oyamo, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 197)
    - "Rococo" by Harry Kondoleon (Box 64, Folder 200)
    - S
      - 1978-1980 (Box 64, Folder 201)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 202)
    - S Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 203)
    - "Sally and Marsha'' by Sybille Pearson, 1979-1981 (Box 65, Folder 204)
    - Schedules and Comments, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 205)
    - Schedules: Lloyd Richards, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 206)
    - Secretary, Office of the
      - 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 207)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 208)
    - Shows, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 209)
    - Shubert Theatre: Board of Directors, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 210)
    - SSDC (Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers), 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 211)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 212)
      - Executive Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 213)
      - Newsletters
        - 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 214)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 215)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, Department of, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 216)
    - Special Theatre Studies Committee, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 218)
    - Spoken in Darkness": Playwrights Project, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 219)
    - Student Correspondence:
      - A-L, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 220)
      - M-Z, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 221)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 222)
    - "The Suicide", 1980 (Box 66, Folder 223)
    - Sunday Series, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 224)
    - T, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 225)
    - T Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 226)
    - T-V, 1978-1980 (Box 66, Folder 227)
    - "The Talisman", 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 228)
    - Teaching Jobs, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 229)
    - TCG (Theatre Communications Group): Board of Directors, 1978-1980 (Box 67, Folder 230)
      - Information, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 231)
      - General Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 232 - 233)
    - Theater Magazine, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 242)
    - Theatre Studies Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 243)
    - "Timon of Athens", 1980 (Box 68, Folder 244)
    - "Twelfth Night", 1980 (Box 68, Folder 245)
    - U, 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 246)
    - UBU Rex, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 247)
    - V, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 248)
    - W, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 249)
    - W Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 250)
    - W-Z, 1978-1980 (Box 69, Folder 251)
    - "Women Beware Women", 1979 (Box 69, Folder 253)
    - Work Study, 1978-1979 (Box 69, Folder 254)
    - Y-Z Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 255)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre:
      - "A Lesson from Aloes", Media Project, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 256)
      - "Aloes" on Broadway and in London, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 257)
      - Applicants for Directing and Design Jobs, 1982-1983 (Box 69, Folder 258)
      - Business Manager, 1981-1983 (Box 69, Folder 259)
      - Casting
        - 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 260)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 70, Folder 261)
      - Contracts, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 262)
      - Managing Director, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 263)
      - Schedule, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 264)
      - Show IV: Hedda Gabler, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 265)
      - Shows: Opening Night, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 266)
      - They Are Dying Out, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 267)
      - UBU, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 268)
      - Winterfest, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 269)
    - Yale School of Drama: Brochure, 1980s (Box 70, Folder 270)
    - "Yerma", 1979 (Box 70, Folder 271)
  - Addendum: Robert Brustein, 1966-1979
    - Financial Plight of Students, 1967-1968 (Box 1A, Folder 1)
    - Yale Theatre, 1968-1972 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Season, 1969-1970 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Season, 1969-1970 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Season, 1970-1971 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
      - Major #1 -- "Story Theatre", 1970-1971 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
      - Major #2 -- "Revenger's Tragedy", 1970-1971 (Box 1A, Folder 7)
      - Major #3 -- "Where Has Tommy Flowers Gone?", 1970-1971 (Box 1A, Folder 8)
      - Major #4 -- "Macbeth", 1970-1971 (Box 1A, Folder 9)
      - Major #5 -- "Woyzeck", 1970-1971 (Box 1A, Folder 10)
      - Major #6 -- "Seven Deadly Sins" and "Little Mahogonny", 1970-1971 (Box 1A, Folder 11)
    - Season, 1971-1972 (Box 1A, Folder 12)
      - Company Members / Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1A, Folder 13)
      - Memos, 1971-1972 (Box 1A, Folder 14)
      - Parties, 1971-1972 (Box 1A, Folder 15)
      - Major #1 -- "When We Dead Awaken", 1971-1972 (Box 2A, Folder 16)
      - Major #2 -- "The Big House", 1971-1972 (Box 2A, Folder 17)
      - Major #3 -- "Caligula", 1971-1972 (Box 2A, Folder 18)
      - Major #4 -- "Repertory Holiday", 1971-1972 (Box 2A, Folder 19)
      - Major #5 -- "I Married You for the Fun of It", 1971-1972 (Box 2A, Folder 20)
      - Major #6 -- "Life is a Dream", 1971-1972 (Box 2A, Folder 21)
    - Season, 1972-1973
      - "Baal", 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 22)
      - "Macbett", 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 23)
      - "Lear", 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 24)
      - "The Bourgeois Gentleman", 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 25)
      - "A Break in The Skin", 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 26)
      - "The Mirror", 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 27)
      - "In The Clap Shack", 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 28)
      - "Are You Now or Have You Ever Been", 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 29)
      - Acting / Directing, 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 31)
      - Design, 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 32)
      - D.F.A., 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 33)
      - Memos, 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 34)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 2A, Folder 35)
      - Playwriting, 1972-1973 (Box 3A, Folder 36)
      - Press, 1972-1973 (Box 3A, Folder 37)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1970-1972 (Box 3A, Folder 38)
    - Special Scripts, 1972-1974 (Box 3A, Folder 39)
    - Student Letters and Information, 1971-1973 (Box 3A, Folder 40)
    - Theses, 1954-1967 (Box 3A, Folder 41)
    - Visitors, 1972-1973 (Box 3A, Folder 42)
    - U-V-W-X-Y-Z, 1972-1973 (Box 3A, Folder 43)
- Records of the dean, 1985-1990; Accession 1991-A-050